Guide to the Stanford University, Program in Human Biology, Lectures [videorecording]
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videos
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Max Weber., Oct 12 1988; V246.162; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Evolution as a Social Concept., Oct 14 1988; V246.163; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Biology, Culture, and the Individual., Oct 17 1988; V246.164; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Language and Human Evolution., Oct 19 1988; V246.165; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. [untitled], Oct 21 1988; V246.166; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf, William Durham. A and B Discussion., Oct 24 1988; V246.167; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. John Rick. Early Hunter-Gatherers., Oct 26 1988; V246.168; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. John Rick. Late Hunter-Gatherers., Oct 28 1988; V246.169; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. John Rick. Origins of Agriculture I., Oct 31 1988; V246.170; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. John Rick. Origins of Agriculture II., Nov 2 1988; V246.171; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. John Rick. Origins of Complex Societies II., Nov 4 1988; V246.172; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Gordon Ringold. Manipulating Gene Expression/Molecular Evolution., Nov 7 1988; V246.173; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Carol Boggs. Ecology: Population Growth., Nov 9 1988; V246.174; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Carol Boggs. Age-Structured Population Growth., Nov 11 1988; V246.175; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Carol Boggs. Population Regulation and Extinction., Nov 14 1988; V246.176; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Origins of the Modern World., Nov 16 1988; V246.177; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Malthus and Marx on Population., Nov 18 1988; V246.178; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. John Rick. Population in Prehistory., Nov 21 1988; V246.179; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Carol Boggs, William Durham, Arthur Wolf. Discussion., Nov 23 1988; V246.180; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. The Origin of World Capitalism., Nov 28 1988; V246.181; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Paul Erlich. Environmental Dimensions of National Security., Nov 30 1988; V246.182; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Family Revolution and Female Emancipation, Dec 2 1988; V246.183; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Craig Heller. Ethology and Animal Behavior, Dec 5 1988; V246.184; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Human Aggression: Case from Amazonia, Dec 7 1988; V246.185; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Carol Boggs, William Durham, Craig Heller, Arthur Wolf. Discussion, Dec 9 1988; V246.186; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Frank Stockdale. Introduction to the Cell, Jan 6 1988; V246.187; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Frank Stockdale. Cells and Tissues I, Jan 8 1988; V246.188; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Frank Stockdale. Cells and Tissues II, Jan 11 1988; V246.189; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Lubert Stryer. Membranes I, Jan 13 1988; V246.190; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Lubert Stryer. Membranes II, Jan 15 1988; V246.191; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Irving Weissman. Immunology I, Jan 20 1988; V246.192; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Irving Weissman. Immunology II, Jan 22 1988; V246.193; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Edgar Engleman. The Human Immune System, Jan 25 1988; V246.194; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Edgar Engleman. AIDS (Second Lecture), Jan 25 1988; V246.195; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Stanley Falkow. Recombinant DNA: Disease, Diagnosis and Vaccines I, Jan 27 1988; V246.196; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Stanley Falkow. Recombinant DNA: Disease, Diagnosis and Vaccines II, Jan 29 1988; V246.197; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Dale Kaiser. Bioenergetics and Muscles, Feb 3 1988; V246.198; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Dale Kaiser. Enzymes, Feb 5 1988; V246.199; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Dale Kaiser. How White Muscles Make ATP, Feb 8 1988; V246.200; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Dale Kaiser. How Red Muscles Make ATP I, Feb 10 1988; V246.201; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Dale Kaiser. How Red Muscles Make ATP II, Feb 12 1988; V246.202; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Virginia Walbot. Plant Development I, Feb 17 1988; V246.203; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Virginia Walbot. Plant Development II, Feb 19 1988; V246.204; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Frank Stockdale. Development II, Feb 26 1988; V246.205; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. David Feldman. Hormones and Development, Feb 29 1988; V246.206; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Merton Bernfield. Human FertilizationBiology 3A[?] Winter 1987/88. Merton Bernfield. Human Fertilization, Mar 4 1988; V246.207; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Merton Bernfield. Human Embryogenesis, Mar 7 1988; V246.208; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Frank Stockdale. Cancer: A Problem in Development, Mar 9 1988; V246.209; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1987/88. Frank Stockdale. Cancer: A Problem in Growth, Mar 11 1988; V246.210; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Frank Stockdale. Introduction to the Cell, Jan 11 1989; V246.211; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Frank Stockdale. Cells and Tissues, Jan 13 1989; V246.212; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Robert Simoni. Membranes and Compartmentalization I, Jan 18 1989; V246.213; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Robert Simoni. Membranes and Compartmentalization II, Jan 20 1989; V246.214; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Ron Levy. Immune System I, Jan 23 1989; V246.215; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Ron Levy. Immune System II, Jan 25 1989; V246.216; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Sanford Dornbusch. Social Psych. Process Schools I, Jan 27 1989; V246.217; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Sanford Dornbusch. Social Psych. Process Schools II, Jan 27 1989; V246.218; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Dale Kaiser. Bioenergetics and Muscles, Jan 30 1989; V246.219; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Dale Kaiser. Enzymes, Feb 1 1989; V246.220; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Dale Kaiser. How White Muscles Make ATP, Feb 3 1989; V246.221; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Anna Spudich. Cytoskeleton: Secretion and Cell Shape, Feb 6 1989; V246.222; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. James Spudich. Cell Motility I, Feb 8 1989; V246.223; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. James Spudich. Cell Motility II, Feb 10 1989; V246.224; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Dale Kaiser. How Red Muscles Make ATP II, Feb 13 1989; V246.225; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Dale Kaiser. How Red Muscles Make ATP III, Feb 15 1989; V246.226; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Sharon Long. Plants: Biochemistry and Development, Feb 17 1989; V246.227; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Sharon Long. Photosynthesis, Feb 22 1989; V246.228; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Merton Bernfield. Differentiation and Morphogenesis, Feb 24 1989; V246.229; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Merton Bernfield. Fertilization and Embryogenesis, Mar 1 1989; V246.230; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Merton Bernfield. Birth, Mar 1 1989; V246.231; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Merton Bernfield. Prematurity, Mar 3 1989; V246.232; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Raymond Hintz. Hormones and Human Growth, Mar 6 1989; V246.233; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Raymond Hintz. Puberty, Mar 8 1989; V246.234; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Gary Schoolnik. Gonorrhea and Infantile Diarrhea, Mar 10 1989; V246.235; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Gary Schoolnik. Gonorrhea and Diarrhea, Mar 10 1989; V246.236; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Frank Stockdale. A Problem in Development, Mar 15 1989; V246.237; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3A Winter 1988/89. Frank Stockdale. A Problem in [?], Mar 17 1989; V246.238; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Albert Hastorf. Social Processes: Affiliation and Attraction, Jan 6 1988; V246.239; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Albert Hastorf. Perception, Jan 8 1988; V246.240; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Albert Hastorf. Social Perception, Jan 11 1988; V246.241; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Sanford Dornbusch. Conformity, Jan 13 1988; V246.242; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Sanford Dornbusch. Inequality, Jan 15 1988; V246.243; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Sanford Dornbusch. Evaluation, Jan 20 1988; V246.244; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Thomas Coates. AIDS Module: Community Education, Jan 27 1988; V246.245; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Sanford Dornbusch. Cognitive Consistency, Jan 29 1988; V246.246; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Herant Katchadourian. Life Cycle I, Feb 1 1988; V246.247; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Herant Katchadourian. Life Cycle II (second lecture), Feb 1 1988; V246.248; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Sanford Dornbusch. Love and Marriage, Feb 3 1988; V246.249; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Becoming a Family, Feb 5 1988; V246.250; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Teen Pregnancy, Feb 8 1988; V246.251; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Attachment, Feb 10 1988; V246.252; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Prematurity, Feb 12 1988; V246.253; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Myra Strober. Women in the Labor Force, Feb 19 1988; V246.254; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Sanford Dornbusch. Gender and Social Structure, Feb 22 1988; V246.255; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Jewelle Gibbs. The Black Family, Feb 26 1988; V246.256; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Aggression, Feb 29 1988; V246.257; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Delinquency, Mar 2 1988; V246.258; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Self-Esteem, Mar 4 1988; V246.259; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Adolescent Development, Mar 7 1988; V246.260; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Themes in Socialization, Mar 11 1988; V246.261; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Albert Hastorf. Social Psychology and Socialization, Jan 11 1989; V246.262; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Albert Hastorf. Cognition and Perception, Jan 13 1989; V246.263; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Albert Hastorf. Social Perception and Perception, Jan 18 1989; V246.264; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Albert Hastorf. Personal and Cognitive Consistency, Jan 20 1989; V246.265; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Albert Hastorf. Conformity, Jan 23 1989; V246.266; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Albert Hastorf. Personal and Cognitive Consistency, Jan 25 1989; V246.267; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Edgar Engleman. AIDS, Jan 30 1989; V246.268; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Thomas Coates. AIDS Prevention Programs (A+B Module), Feb 1 1989; V246.269; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Sanford Dornbusch. Inequalities in Interaction, Feb 3 1989; V246.270; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Herant Katchadourian. Transition to Families: Life Cycle I, Feb 6 1989; V246.271; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Herant Katchadourian. Life Cycle II, Feb 8 1989; V246.272; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Jerry Talley. Love and Marriage, Feb 10 1989; V246.273; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Shirley Feldman. Becoming a Family, Feb 13 1989; V246.274; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 20)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Shirley Feldman. Teen Pregnancy, Feb 15 1989; V246.275; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Shirley Feldman. Development Attachment, Feb 17 1989; V246.276; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Shirley Feldman. Prematurity, Feb 22 1989; V246.277; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Myra Strober. Daycare, Feb 24 1989; V246.278; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Shirley Feldman. Aggression and Delinquency, Feb 27 1989; V246.279; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Sanford Dornbusch. Puberty, Feb 27 1989; V246.280; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Shirley Feldman. Sextyping, Mar 3 1989; V246.281; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Shirley Feldman. Self, Mar 6 1989; V246.282; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Families, Mar 10 1989; V246.283; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Sanford Dornbusch. New Families and Children, Mar 13 1989; V246.284; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Sanford Dornbusch. Single Parent Family, Mar 13 1989; V246.285; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 3B Winter 1988/89. Jewelle Gibbs. Black Families, Mar 17 1989; V246.286; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. Jeffrey Wine. Information Transmission in the Nervous System, Apr 3 1987; V246.287; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. Roland Ciaranello. Neurochemistry Basics, Apr 13 1987; V246.288; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. Dennis Baylor. Transduction in the Visual System, Apr 17 1987; V246.289; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. Carla Shatz. Integration in the Visual System, Apr 20 1987; V246.290; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. Carla Shatz. Development of the Visual System, Apr 22 1987; V246.291; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller. Ingest/Digestion, May 11 1987; V246.292; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller. Absorption/Fuel Metabolism, May 13 1987; V246.293; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. James Lawry. Cardiovascular/Heart, May 18 1987; V246.294; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. James Lawry. Cardiovascular/The Vasculature/Heart, May 18/87, 5/20 1987; V246.295; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1987/88. H. Craig Heller. Homeostasis, Mar 30 1988; V246.296; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1987/88. Roland Ciaranello. Neurochemistry Basics, Apr 11 1988; V246.297; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1987/88. H. Craig Heller. [untitled], Apr 25 1988; V246.298; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1987/88. Donald Kennedy. [untitled], Jun 1 1988; V246.299; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Jeffrey Wine. Information Transmission in the Nervous System, Apr 1 1989; V246.300; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Jeffrey Wine. Transmembrane Potential, Apr 4 1989; V246.301; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. Homeostasis, Apr 5 1989; V246.302; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Jeffrey Wine. Nerve Impulse, Apr 6 1989; V246.303; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Jeffrey Wine. Synaptic Transmission, Apr 8 1989; V246.304; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Dennis Baylor. Transduction in the Visual System, Apr 15 1989; V246.305; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Jared Tinklenberg. Alzheimers Disease, Apr 19 1989; V246.306; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Susan McConnell. Integration in the Visual System, Apr 24 1989; V246.307; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Susan McConnell. Development of the Visual System, Apr 26 1989; V246.308; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. Neuroendicrine Regulation and Behavior [9am], May 1 1989; V246.309; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. Neuroendicrine Regulation and Behavior[10am], May 1 1989; V246.310; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. Hormones and Behavior, May 1 1989; V246.311; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Herant Katchadourian. Hormones and Behavior, May 3 1989; V246.312; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. Autonomic Nervous System, May 5 1989; V246.313; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. James Lawry. The Heart, May 8 1989; V246.314; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. James Lawry. The Vascular System, May 10 1989; V246.315; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. James Lawry. Regulation of Cardiovascular Function, May 15 1989; V246.316; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. Respiratory Gas Exchange I, May 17 1989; V246.317; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. Respiratory Gas Exchange II, May 19 1989; V246.318; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. James Lawry. Ingestion and Digestion, May 24 1989; V246.319; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. James Lawry. Fuel Metabolism, May 26 1989; V246.320; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. Salt Water Balance, May 31 1989; V246.321; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. The Kidney, Jun 2 1989; V246.322; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1988/89. Craig Heller. Metabolism in Rest and Exercise, Jun 5 1989; V246.323; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Herant Katchadourian. Hormones and Sexual Behavior, Apr 24 1987; V246.324; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Herant Katchadourian. Hormones and Gender Identity, Apr 27 1987; V246.325; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. David Maron. Risk Factors in Heart Disease/Prevention of Heart Disease, May 20/87, 5/22 1987; V246.326; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1987/88. Shirley Feldman. Conflict in the Family: Child Abuse, Apr 11 1988; V246.327; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1987/88. Stephen Lovett. Alzheimers: Psychological Aspects, Apr 19 1988; V246.328; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1987/88. Jared Tinklenberg. Drug Abuse, Apr 28 1988; V246.329; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. Herant Katchadourian. Hormones and Gender, May 3 1989; V246.330; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. Stephanie Brown. Alcohol: Problem or Solution, May 5 1989; V246.331; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. David Maron. Risk Factors in Heart Disease, May 8 1989; V246.332; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. David Maron. Risk Factors in Heart Disease, May 10 1989; V246.333; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. David Maron. Preventing Heart Disease, May 10 1989; V246.334; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. Donald Kennedy. Dimensions of Environmental Destruction, May 15 1989; V246.335; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. John Wirth. Environmental Management: Brazil/Mexico, May 17 1989; V246.336; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. William Durham. Destruction of Rain Forests: Ecological Impact, May 19 1989; V246.337; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. William Durham. Destruction of Rain Forests: Native Impact, May 22 1989; V246.338; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. Peter Vitousek. Changing Composition of Atmosphere, May 24 1989; V246.339; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. Harold Mooney. Solving Global Environmental Problems, May 26 1989; V246.340; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. Herant Katchadourian. Death and Bereavement, May 27 1989; V246.341; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. Paul Erlich. Population Regulation in Rich Countries, Jun 2 1989; V246.342; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)